FLORIN MARIUS DRILEA

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

As a highly reliable Software Engineer with a strong academic background in Computer Science. Well-versed in multiple programming languages, experienced in working in Agile environments and maintain a consistent eagerness to learn and grow in my field.

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER 10/2021 to Current

Sky Betting and Gaming, Leeds, UK

- Worked on the development of Sky Bet Club, one of the most complicated and extensible promotions, using Scala, Kafka Streams and GraphQL.
- Developed new code for different software projects, and ensured that it was well-tested.
- Supported code review, system integration, and validation in line with company requirements.

GRADUATE SOFTWARE ENGINEER 02/2021 to 09/2021

The Hut Group, Manchester, UK

- Worked with microservices in an agile programming environment using Java Spring Framework.
- Maintained the existing microservices and built new ones based on required features.
- Built a web application that tracked the work done by language translators using Java and Spring.

GAME SERVER DEVELOPER 07/2020 to 09/2020

Crucible, Sheffield, UK

- Built a game engine and developed the servers for various types of slot games using an internal library, GDM game engine.
- Wrote well-designed and efficient code to develop the backend of slot games.

JUNIOR JAVA DEVELOPER 07/2019 to 10/2019

UniCredit Services, Iasi, Romania

• Worked on a project named TFO during an internship at UniCredit Services using Java 8 and data sets to transfer data from OCR reading to specific locations.

SKILLS

- Java
- Spring
- Scala
- JavaScript
- Python

- MySQL
- Couchbase
- REST
- Kafka
- Kubernetes

- Jenkins
- CI/CD
- Hibernate
- JIRA
- GIT

EDUCATION

University of Sheffield, Sheffield, England

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science, July, 2020

- Web officer of Romanian Society
- Student Ambassador and Mentor
- Achieved 2.1

LANGUAGES